[Music]
I don't mind having a big beautiful door
in that wall so that people can come
into this country
legally and of course above that door it
says Donald Trump presents America
somebody's doing the
raping how's that poptart doing it's not
going well consequences to show that
treat everyone the same here in
America
oh Ricky you didn't make it what
happened how was I supposed to make it
there wasn't enough time Larry 31
seconds if I were able to figure out
what Trump was trying to say I would
kill
myself there's no way in hell I want to
be in Trump's head there's no way okay
there's no way I don't get it man I
don't it's like one of those questions
you can't answer why do women support I
don't know why are there poor
Republicans I don't know these are
things I don't get right hey America
Larry Wilmore here if you like the
nightly show on Comedy Central like us
on Facebook too just don't poke me I do
not like being poked you can Candy Crush
me